const qBank = [
    {
      question:
        "What is the most important thing about a friendship to you?",
      answers: ["Have somebody to confide in", "Have somebody to have fun with"],
      questionId: "1"
    },
    {
      question:
        'Would you rather...',
      answers: ["Have a friend who enjoys doing the same things as you", "Have a friend who feels the same way about life as you do"],
      questionId: "2"
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which statement below do you relate the most?",
      answers: ["I like to be close to people", "I like to keep my distance from people"],
      questionId: "3"
    },
    {
      question: "When you talk with friends on the phone, it is usually to?",
      answers: [
        "Make arrangements or plans",
        "Have a conversation or chat"
      ],
      questionId: "4"
    },
    {
      question: "Which statement below do you relate the most?",
      answers: ["I like to plan where I am going and who I am going with", "I like to be spontaneous and just let fate decide"],
      questionId: "5"
    },
    {
      question: "You are going to the movies, which genre would you likely choose?",
      answers: ["Action", "Drama"],
      questionId: "6"
    },
    {
      question: "If you are meeting a friend, what activity would you prefer doing?",
      answers: ["Shopping", "Playing at the Arcade"],
      questionId: "7"
    },
    {
      question: "If you moved to a new city, which would you rather put more effort into?",
      answers: ["Staying in touch with old friends", "Making new friends"],
      questionId: "8"
    },
    {
      question: "As a friend, you are someone that?",
      answers: ["Supports others", "Is fun to be with"],
      questionId: "9"
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do when your friend has a problem",
      answers: ["Discuss their feelings", "Come up with practical solutions"],
      questionId: "10"
    },
    {
      question: "If your friend was having personal problems, what do you do?",
      answers: ["Wait for them to contact you", "Contact them to discuss the problem"],
      questionId: "11"
    },
    {
      question: "What do you do when you have a personal problem?",
      answers: ["I work it out on my own", "I share it with a friend"],
      questionId: "12"
    },
    {
      question: "When talking with friends, which of the topics below are you more interested to talk about?",
      answers: ["Political and current affairs", "Hobbies and interests"],
      questionId: "13"
    },
    {
      question: "When talking with friends, which of the topics below are you more interested to talk about?",
      answers: ["Family and friends", "Work or school"],
      questionId: "14"
    },
    {
      question: "When talking to someone you just met, which of the topics below are you more interested to talk about?",
      answers: ["Political and current affairs", "Hobbies and interests"],
      questionId: "15"
    },
    {
      question: "When talking to someone you just met, which of the topics below are you more interested to talk about?",
      answers: ["Family and friends", "Work or school"],
      questionId: "16"
    }
  ];
  
  export default () => Promise.resolve(qBank);
  